Finding Aid for Catalogs of Michigan-based automobile companies, 1896-1971 and undated
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Packard Motor Car Co.,- Winton Motor Co.
  - Willys-Overland Co., Toledo, Ohio
    - 3 specification sheets for ambulances Undated (Box 5)
    - O novo Aero Willys (in Portuguese) Undated (Box 5)
  - Winton Motor Carriage Co., Cleveland, Ohio (Box 5)
    - Winton six colors Undated (Box 5)
    - Winton six body designs in outline 1910 (Box 5)
    - Winton six 1910 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous
  - List of automobile advertising slogans (Box 5)
  - Invitation to subscribe to the Gallery of the American Automobile circa 1964 (Box 5)
  - Roll call of 2,530 automobiles sold in America during the past 50 years or more, compiled for the automobile industry by The Saturday Evening Post [wall poster, ca. 1950] (Box 5)
  - This Week Magazine December 2, 1956 (Box 5)
  - [The Auto Motor Journal] Illustrated buyer's guide to the cars of 1912 (Box 5)
  - "Get a horse" [color photographs of antique cars], Family Circle September 1954 (Box 5)
  - National Automobile Show official program 1956 (Box 5)